https://www.belfastgiants.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentTitle sponsor: Stena Line
It's a giant game day!Belfast Giants play the
TONIGHT at
1AM — Miss it / miss out! Buy + Print Tickets Get the SSE Arena App WATCH Live StreamOfficial website of the Stena Line Belfast Giants
Belfast Giants HomeTeamSchedule + ticketsNewsContactStorePrivacy Notice for The Belfast GiantsWe want you to know that when you use our organisation you can trust us with your information. We are determined to do nothing that would infringe your rights or undermine your trust. This Privacy Notice describes the information we collect about you, how it is used and shared, and your rights regarding it.Data ControllerOML Belfast Ltd is registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) as a Data Controller for the personal data that we hold and process. Our registered address is 2 Queen’s Quay, Belfast, BT3 9QQ and our registration number is Z6718093. Our Data Protection Lead can be contacted at data@theodyssey.co.uk. Data CollectionAll of the information that we hold about you is provided to us by yourself when you seek to use our services.We will tell you why we need the information and how we will use it.Our Lawful Basis for processing your informationThe General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) requires all organisations that process personal data to have a Lawful Basis for doing so.The Lawful Bases identified in the GDPR are:Consent of the data subjectPerformance of a contract with the data subject or to take steps to enter into a contractCompliance with a legal obligationTo protect the vital interests of a data subject or another personPerformance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller.The legitimate interests of ourselves, or a third party, except where such interests are overridden by the interests, rights or freedoms of the data subject.Examples of legitimate interests include:Where the data subject is a client or in the service of the controller;Transmission within a group of undertakings for internal administrative purposes;Processing necessary to ensure network and information security, including preventing unauthorised access;Processing for direct marketing purposes, or to prevent fraud; andReporting possible criminal acts or threats to public security.Our lawful basis is consent of the data subject or performance of a contract with the data subject or to take steps to enter a contract and our legitimate interest is processing for direct marketing purposes.We use your information to:Provide goods, services, deliveries, quotations, and information, for example newsletters;Process or support payments for goods and services;Conduct data analysis, testing, and research (including for product development), and to monitor and analyse usage and activity trends;Maintain the safety, security and integrity of our services;Direct your enquiries to the appropriate customer support staff;Investigate and address your concerns;Communicate with you about products, services, promotions, surveys, news, updates and events;Process promotions/competitions, including prizes, and send you information about our services and those of our business partners;Investigate or address legal proceedings relating to your use of our services/products, or as otherwise allowed by applicable law;Make statutory returns as requiredWe do not use automated decision-making in the processing of your personal data.We collect and process both personal data and special categories of personal data as defined in the GDPR. This includes:Customer dataName;Email;Phone number;Address;Payment or bank details;Date of birth;Location details;Device IP address and MAC addressCCTV ImagesCustomer correspondenceCookies including Facebook and Google AnalyticsWe may share your personal data with:Partners that help us to deliver our goods and servicesOur fellow subsidiaries of the Odyssey Trust GroupOur legal advisors in the event of a dispute or other legal matter;Law enforcement officials, government authorities, or other third parties to meet our legal obligations;In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, consolidation or restructuring, financing, refinancing, or acquisition of some or all of our business by another company;Any other party where we ask you and you consent to the sharing.Transfers to third countries and international organisations:We transfer personal data to the following third countries or international organisations using the identified safeguards because of email marketing purposes.We use MailChimp for email marketing. MailChimp’s servers are located in the EU and the United States. Their privacy policy can be found at https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/Retention:We retain your personal data white you remain a customer as per our Retention and Disposal Policy. This policy details how long we hold data for and how we dispose of it when it no longer needs to be held. We will delete or anonymise your information at your request unless:There is an unresolved issue, such as claim or dispute;We are legally required to; orThere are overriding legitimate business interests, including but not limited to fraud prevention and protecting customers’ safety and security.Your RightsThe General Data Protection Regulation gives you specific rights around your personal data. For example, you have to be informed about the information we hold and what we use it for, you can ask for a copy of the personal information we hold about you, you can ask us to correct any inaccuracies with the personal data we hold, you can ask us to stop sending you direct mail, or emails, or in some circumstances ask us to stop processing your details. Finally, if we do something irregular or improper with your personal data you can seek compensation for any distress you are caused or loss you have incurred. You can find out more information from the ICO’s website http://ico.org.uk/for_the_public/personal_information and this is the organisation that you can complain to if you are unhappy with how we deal with you. You also have the right to erasure.Accessing and Correcting Your InformationYou may request access to, correction of, or a copy of your information by contacting us at data@theodyssey.co.ukWe will not charge a fee for a subject access request.Unsubscribe from MarketingYou may unsubscribe from receiving emails and other messages from our organisation by following the instructions in those messages. CookiesCookies are small text files that are stored on your browser or device by websites, apps, online media, and advertisements. We use cookies to:Validate users;For E-commerce tracking;Remember user preferences and settings;Determine frequency of accessing our content;Measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns on platforms such as Facebook and Google Analytics; andAnalyse site visits and trends.We will occasionally update our Privacy Notice. When we make significant changes that are relevant to you we will notify you of these by email. We will publish the updated Notice on our website.Next FixtureNew season fixtures coming soon! 2020/21 SEASON TICKETS DetailsApplication GIANTS IN THE COMMUNITY
More infoPost navigationErrorHome
